CHEERS! THRILLS! LAUGHS!
The Sophomore is a comedy film directed by Leo McCarey.
Joe Collins arrives at Hanford College to begin his second year with $200 to pay his tuition, is enticed into a craps game, and loses
all in this nostalgic slice of college, replete with songs, romance, prom dances and the inevitable big football game.
Joe Collins, played by Eddie Quillan.
Margie Callahan, played by Sally O'Neil.
Tom Weck, played by Stanley Smith.
Barbara Lange, played by Jeanette Loff.
Dutch, played by Russell Gleason.
Mrs. Collins, played by Sarah Padden.
A sophomore in American English is a student in the second
year of study at high school or college.
Sophomore or Sophomores may also refer to:
"Sophomore" (song), a song by Ciara from her self-titled 2013 album
Fleetwings BT-12
Sophomore, a 1940s American trainer airplane
The Sophomore, a 1929 American comedy film directed by Leo McCarey
The tone is lighthearted.